Dad!
爸爸！
No.
不对
-She is not Hikari. -What?
-她不是日花里 -什么？
She is not my daughter!
她不是我女儿！
Where is Hikari? Where have you hidden her?
日花里在哪里？ 你把日花里藏去哪了？
Who… are you?
你是谁？
Oops, he outed me.
真可惜 露馅了
Of course.
当然了
I can't possibly mistake you for my real daughter.
谁会认错自己的亲生女儿？
-Have you all been deceived? -But…
-你们想骗我？ -不是的
Where did you find a girl who looks exactly like…
她长得几乎一样
Don't tell me… She has received plastic surgery?
该不会是整容吧？
You put a little girl through that?
她还这么小
Rainman has even done something that cruel?
雨人居然这么狠？
I'm sorry, Keebou, for deceiving you.
对不起 希少 我撒谎了
Just like what that lady said,
就跟那个姐姐说的一样
It was easy to deceive you, because you're an idiot!
希少你太容易骗了 真是个笨蛋
You weren't even aware of it at all and helped me with all your might.
完全没有发现 还拼了命救我
Thank you for even making stewed beef for me.
谢谢你做炖牛肉给我吃
She lied about something that Keebou would know was a lie.
她可能是特地说了个 希少会知道的谎话
I mean the stewed beef. She did it to let us know that she was lying.
那个炖牛肉 让我们知道她在撒谎
What the heck, stupid kid?
臭丫头 你开什么玩笑！ 把我们耍得团团转
Where is the real Hikari?
真的日花里在哪？
Where have you hidden her?
到底在哪里？
My daughter…
日花里…
Let me see Hikari!
我要见女儿
Shut up! Tell us the passwords now! Or I'll kill you.
闭嘴！快说要怎么样解锁 不然杀了你
Kill me if you want.
想杀就杀！
The data…
你们就永远别想读取卡片内容
Have you any clue where she is?
那你有头绪没有？
The deadline is approaching.
时间不多了
I don't know what has happened,
我是不知道怎么了
but if she is a fake, then we should find the real one first.
既然她是冒牌货 首先该去抓住真的
Where do you think?
那你说呢？
It's either the basement of the mountain villa
不是在山上别墅的地下室 就在中根湖的船屋
I told her to stay there if anything happened.
我说过有事就待在那里 里面粮食也充足
because she is a clever girl.
应该会听我的话待在那里
You guys will go with them.
喂 你们一起去
Mr. Sendagi.
是 老大
Don't worry about that.
用不着你操心
We will take care of this.
交给我们办吧
We'll go, too, just in case.
这是怕有什么意外 大师
-Go now. -Yes, sir…
-快去 -是
Are you worrying that we will steal a march on you?
你怕我们会抢功劳吗？
When you have been in a business that involves violence for a long time,
我的江山是用暴力打下来的
you become very cautious.
别怪我多疑
You can't do anything about it, then.
这也难怪
Because this has been ingrained
这就是人家说的
in your character.
江山易改 本性难移
We can deal with their number now.
这个人数有胜算
Three per person.
一个对三个
Let's go.
上
-Tagawa. -Yes, sir.
-田川 -在
Kill the kid.
把那小鬼做掉
What…
什么？
It doesn't matter, does it?
我想你应该不不介意吧？
She is a stranger to you.
反正她是个陌生人
With all due respect,
恕我直言 只怕她是雨人的人 不杀为妙
I'll say this for future reference, Tagawa.
田川 给我记住
You're not the one to decide that, I am.
做主的是我 不是你
Just go and do it!
不用管 把她做掉！
That's it, Tagawa.
很好 田川
My will is yours.
我的意志就是你的意志
-Kill her! -Chancellor!
-把她做掉！ -总长
Dad!
爸爸！
I knew it.
我就知道
You deceived us?
居然演戏
This is absurd.
怎么回事？
Tell us how to unlock the data now!
说 怎么样才能解锁！
Mr. Sakaki.
大师
Let me handle this.
这里我来处理
Tagawa.
田川
Shoot her in the limbs first.
先从四肢开始打
Right leg.
右腿
Left leg.
左腿
Right arm.
右手
Left arm.
左手
-No! -The way to unlock it!
-住手！ -怎么解锁？
-Chancellor! -Tagawa!
-总长！ -田川！
-Shoot! -No!
-开枪！ -住手！
I'll say it… I will tell you!
我说…
-What are you doing, idiot? -Shut up, old man.
-混蛋 你干嘛！ -闭嘴 老头
I'll stay true to myself.
我就是我自己
Chancellor…
总长…
There are rules to obey when you fight.
打架也有规则
Never betray your friends and never harm women and children.
不出卖伙伴 不对女人的和孩子动手
-Don't move! Or I'll kill him! -Stop there!
-都别动 不然我把老头做掉！ -别动！
Go! Take the kid and her dad and run.
走 带着小鬼和她爸走
-But, Chancellor… -Don't mind me, just go!
-但是 总长… -好了 快走！
-Don't let them go! -I told you not to move!
-别让他们跑了！ -我说不许动！
If you want to kill him,
想杀他的话…
do it, then.
就杀吧
What was that, jerk?
你胡说什么？
Aren't you working together?
你们不是一伙的吗？
We work together?
一伙的？
Please don't get this wrong.
你误会了 真伤脑筋
We are not at the same rank.
我跟他等级不一样
You are under me.
你在我之下
Of course you are.
这是当然的
Why would you, a barbarian, and me, the messenger of God,
我乃神的使者 为何要跟野蛮的黑道
be standing on the same stage?
站同一个舞台上？
Do you really think someone like you will be useful to our ideal country?
像你这种人 在理想国能有什么贡献？
You are barking mad.
他已经疯了
Capture the father
抓住小鬼的父亲
and make him tell us the way to unlock the data.
逼他说出解密方法
Hikari!
日花里！
You, too!
你们也上
Are you sure?
你们想清楚了吗？会长不讲仁义的
you can't go anywhere later after the old man dies or I die.
老头或我一死 你们就走投无路
How foolish…
多么愚蠢
you gangsters are.
黑道就是蠢
You…
喂 你们休想活着离开
If I can't go by tomorrow, I'll have to pay a late fee for my DVD.
我还得回去还DVD 不然会被罚款的
Hikari!
日花里
Get lost!
给我滚！
-Chancellor! -Just go!
-总长！ -别管我 快走！
Sorry, I've never been able to help you much.
抱歉 我总是只能帮小忙
That's not the case at all!
怎么会是小忙？你帮大忙了 总长
Go!
走！
How dare you, jerk?
你这混蛋！
What are you doing?
你在干什么？
Sorry, Tenten, please pull over.
典典 不好意思 停车
Why?
为什么？
-Miki, you have to use the toilet? -I'm going back.
-米奇哥 要上厕所吗？ -我要回去
What are you saying, Miki?
你说什么 米奇哥？
Don't be ridiculous.
别说傻话
-Why, Miki? -You're returning for Chancellor?
-为什么 米奇？ -你是想救总长？
-I'll go with you. -No.
-那我也去 -不必 一个人比较好行动
-You can't do that alone! -No, Miki…
-一个人没办法的 -别这样 米奇
Miki.
米奇
Who are you?
你是谁？
I am myself.
我是我自己
-Get Chancellor out of there. -Sure.
-总长就拜托你了 -好
-Miki!
-米奇 -米奇哥
Idiot!
混蛋！
I didn't know you were so old.
真没想到你会这么做
I'm disappointed, Tagawa.
太让我失望了 田川
How dare you…
-混蛋！
I've always wanted to do this.
我想试很久了
Because someone did it to me the other day.
我以前也曾被人吐口水
Kill him 100 times and bury him!
我要你死一百次！
You idiot, Tagawa!
可恶 田川！
Hikari.
日花里
You have…
你真的…
done very well.
很努力
Dad!
爸爸
I'm sorry.
对不起
I'm sorry, Hikari.
对不起 日花里
Dad…
爸爸
I'm sorry.
对不起
I want to go back there.
我还是想回去
For Miki?
去找米奇吗？
Miki will be all right.
放心 米奇没事的
I know Miki is very strong,
我知道米奇哥很强 但对方人多势众
You know,
每当米奇说
when Miki says that, "It's easier to go alone,"
“一个人比较好行动”
Then he'll win in a second and come back.
因为过不久 他就会打赢回来
-Right? -Yeah, it's Miki's…
-对 -这就是米奇
"It's easier to go alone" legend, isn't it?
“一个人比较好行动”的传说
Hey!
站起来！
It's too early to pass out, idiot.
站起来 混蛋
Get yourself together!
醒醒
-We haven't finished with you! -Get up…
-还没完呢 混蛋 -站起来
I've put you through such a tough time, haven't I?
真的让你们受苦了
This is…
我真的不知道该说些什么
Please don't say that, Mr. Goto.
请别这样 伯父
At that time, too…
那时候我心想只要让日花里来
then your friends would come with you,
你的朋友们也会一起来
then I might manage to run away from there.
到时候或许就有办法逃脱
-I bet on that possibility. -I knew it.
-所以我才冒险赌了一把 -果然
You are the last hope of this country.
你们是这个国家最后的希望
Please. I hope you'll…
拜托 请实现我最后的愿望
So that was what your words meant.
原来那番话是这个意思
Hikari, well done for knowing
日花里一下就明白我的想法 看出我在说谎
I knew it at once.
我马上就知道了
Because I am who I am.
因为我就是我自己
I thought you must have a reason for lying there,
我知道爸爸撒谎一定会有苦衷
so I pretended that I was not Hikari.
所以我也假装自己不是自己
Did you?
这样啊
Just like my last birthday.
跟去年生日时一样
Oh, you mean the present?
是 生日礼物那时候
Hikari's wit
日花里十分聪明
has protected us many times.
保护了我们很多遍
What? Protected? I protected you guys?
保护你们？我吗？
What are you going to do then?
接下来有什么打算
I think we will escape abroad for a while.
我想暂时到外国避避风头
I have put our passports and necessities in a trunk room
为以防万一 我把护照和随身物
near the airport if the crunch comes.
都寄放在机场附近的储物柜里
I see.
这样啊
But I hid the key in the mountain villa,
只是钥匙则藏在山上的别墅
I hope they didn't take it…
希望没有被拿走
Oh, Keebou, the keys!
希少 那把钥匙
These ones?
这个
This is the key!
就是这个
-You're a lifesaver! Thank you! -Don't mention it.
-太好了 谢谢 -不会
But Mr. Goto, the data
伯父 可是存储卡…
was still taken by the Glorious Ark in the end. Sorry for that.
还是在光耀方舟手上 对不起
-No, it isn't your fault. -But…
-这不能怪你们 -但是…
It was a golden opportunity to bring Rainman to the light, but…
本来是让雨人曝光的大好机会
In the end,
但或许命运早注定会变成这样
Let's go.
等一下
Sorry…
不好意思 请让我们上车
Sorry to interrupt, but can I borrow that?
打扰了 机车借我行吗？
-What? -Make a call.
-什么？ -打电话 来
-Who should I call? -You, of course! Do it now.
-打去哪？ -打给你 快
Thanks. I'll call you after I finish using it.
抱歉 用完了再打给你
It's for the taxi.
给你 出租车的费用
And this is for your hotel room.
还有旅馆费
Have fun.
玩开心点
Let's go to a hotel.
我说啊 去开房间吧
Sure!
好
Aren't you guys too cold to Miki?
大家对米奇哥太冷漠了
If it were Keebou, you'd have gone to rescue him ages ago.
换成希少哥 大家肯定会去帮他
That's because Keebou always makes us worried.
因为希少总让人操心
-He cries very easily. -He's good at fighting, though.
-也很容易哭 -虽然打架很厉害
Miki is all right on his own.
放心 米奇一个人没事的
Miki named us Who Are You.
风爱友也是米奇想出来的
There are three things that are important to him.
他珍惜三件事
Wind,
风
love,
爱
and friends,
朋友
I know what love and friends mean, but what is wind?
爱和友我理解 风是什么？
He said "wind" meant freedom.
风是“自由”的意思
-Freedom? -Yeah.
-自由？ -对
There is a fine line between love and friends,
爱和友只要错一步 就会变成束缚和脚镣
So he told us to never forget
所以要让别人和你自己 像风一样自由
To give another person freedom means that you have to trust them, Melos.
梅洛斯 要让对方自由 就只能相信对方
As in, I trust you so I'll let you do whatever you please.
我相信你 所以让你放手去做
Oh, stop worrying about him!
别愁眉苦脸了
He never does anything blindly.
他不是有勇无谋的人
He acts when the timing is right.
一定会看准时机才出手
Well, he used to be pretty hotheaded, both Choco and him.
不过以前他和阿闪也真是…
What do you mean?
什么？
He would be beside himself when he saw red.
一生气就冲昏头
They were a mad dog duo.
是一对疯狗搭档
That is surprising.
真有点意外
Then Keebou came up with what we always say.
所以希少就想出了那招牌动作
Like reminding them not to get carried away and go to pick a fight.
提醒他们别像疯狗般乱冲乱撞
It's what we say before we fight,
打架前得说
Who are you?
-你是谁？
Idiot!
混蛋 醒来
You can't get up?
已经昏过去了？
You look so pitiable, Mr. Chancellor.
总长先生 你真丢脸
People said you were the strongest when you were a kid, right?
小时候 别人都说你最强
You were unbeatable in the countryside, huh?
原来只是乡下的井底之蛙
Unbeatable is an overstatement.
说我没输过太夸张了
There were people who I couldn't beat easily.
我就是打不过某个人
You still have the energy to talk, huh?
你还有力气说话
Especially when…
那个人…
he was still called a mad dog.
以前被称为“疯狗”
Who the heck are you?
你是谁？
I am myself.
我是我自己
Idiots.
你这蠢蛋
Who… You're…
你是…
Ouch!
痛…
I see you're awake.
你醒来了
What is this, a dream?
这是梦吗？
Stop blowing that.
别吹了
Ponjara!
碰将
The wound required quite a few stitches,
缝了很多针 不过脑部正常
How did he get injured?
怎么会这样？
-I was going to give the data… -What?
-因为我把存储卡… -什么？
My son has a heart disease,
我儿子有心脏病
and someone from the Glorious Ark told me to give them the data
光耀方舟的人说 想让他动手术就交出存储卡
I was going to give it to her.
我打算给他们
Then this happened…
便弄成这样
I'm really sorry!
真的对不起
Hang on a minute…
等一下
But I had the data…
存储卡明明由我保管着
This data is not real?
存储卡是假的？怎么回事 美史？
It was swapped.
存储卡被人掉包了
Mr. Segawa didn't realize that,
濑川先生自己也不知道 便把假的给了姊姊你们
Where is the real data?
真的存储卡在哪里？
Do you know where it is?
你知道吗？
Yes, I do.
我知道
I didn't do it because I didn't trust you.
绝不是不信任你 这是警察的常用手法
when we have to guard some important data.
以保护重要的情报
I'll keep it until then.
还是由我保管吧
I think I should keep it.
不 还是由我来
-Oh, that was when… -Yeah.
-就在那时候 -对
You saved the day, Mr. Oshima. Thank you!
实在太好了 大岛先生 谢谢你
Why?
什么？
Actually, our SD card was taken away.
-其实我的存储卡被人拿走了 -这样啊
That's…
存储卡在…
NUMBER WITHHELD
（未显示号码来电）
Yes?
是
What?
什么？
Look.
你看
Miki!
米奇哥！
Hey, Melos.
梅洛斯
Ow…
好痛…
What's the matter? I just didn't come back last night. Let's go.
你干什么？ 我才去了一个晚上而已 走吧
WHO ARE YOU
（风爱友）
Mifumi.
美史
Futaba.
姊姊…
I told you to come alone!
我不是叫你一个人来吗？
Where is the data? We have no time.
存储卡呢？没时间了
I haven't got it with me now.
不在我手上
Then why did you call me here?
那叫我出来干嘛？
If I didn't,
我不这样做的话 姊姊
you would look for Mr. Segawa
你会去找濑川先生
and kill him, wouldn't you?
然后杀了他 对吧？
Did you lie to me?
你骗我？
No, I really have the data.
不 我已拿到存储卡了 真的
Then bring it here now!
那就快交出来
I will.
姊姊
If you promise to leave…
只要你答应离开光耀方舟
the Glorious Ark.
我就交给你
What are you saying?
你胡说什么？
Atone
请姊姊你好好赎罪
I will be
我会一直等下去
You…
你怎么会变成这样…
Why?
你怎么会来？
-You traitor! -No!
-叛徒！ -不是的
Miss Mifumi wasn't the one who called me here.
不是美史小姐叫我来的
What?
什么？
That person told me that Miss Mifumi
是那个人说的
wanted to rescue you, so she pretended to be brainwashed
美史小姐是为了救你才假装被洗脑
and infiltrated into the Glorious Ark.
潜入光耀方舟
You have been deceiving me right from the beginning?
你一开始就在骗我？
I just wanted you to come home,
我很想要姊姊你回来
Please come back.
回来吧
Come back?
回来？
To where?
回去哪？
There is not a place I can return to.
我已无家可归
I have ruined everything.
全被我自己毁掉了
-Futaba… -You, too.
-姊姊 -其实你心里也恨我 对吧？
-I don't hate… -Liar!
-我不恨你… -撒谎！
It was all my fault.
不就是我的错吗？
I was responsible for both Mom's and Dad's deaths.
妈妈的死 还有爸爸的死
-It was not your fault! -Yes, it was.
-不是姊姊的错 -都是我
If I hadn't asked Mom to go out with me that day,
要不是我受不了诱惑
she wouldn't have had an accident.
妈妈就不会遇上意外
If Mom were alive
妈妈没死
-then Dad wouldn't have killed himself. -No…
-爸爸也不会自杀 -不是的
It was my fault.
都是我的错
-It wasn't your fault! -It was my fault!
-不是你的错 -是我的错！
It is obvious! Don't think that I'm stupid.
我很清楚 别把我当傻瓜
A person kills themself because they don't want to do anything,
寻死是因为什么都不想做了 什么都不想知道
know anything, see anything and hear anything.
什么都不想看 什么都不想听
That's why people kill themselves.
所以才会寻死
Futaba!
姊姊
You suffered a lot, didn't you?
我知道你已经受了很多苦
So many times…
已经不知道
You've tried so many times to kill yourself.
想自杀多少遍了
-So please… -If I could die…
-所以不要再… -能死的话
I would have been dead ages ago.
我老早去死了
I couldn't die,
我连死都死不了
but I couldn't live as well.
但也活不下去
Then I met the Hierarch.
那时候我遇见了大师
He hugged me tightly…
他紧紧抱着我
and thanked me for staying alive.
说：“谢谢你活了下来
He said that he would give me a purpose to live.
我会赋予你生存的意义”
So I…
所以我…
Give me the data.
把存储卡交出来
I will continue to live for the Hierarch.
我这一生都要为大师而活
You're right.
对
It was your fault.
都是你的错
It was your fault that…
你父母死去都是你的错
But this is what you think from the bottom of your heart, isn't it?
反正你是这么想的 打从心底里
Choco,
阿闪
who you shot,
那个被你枪击的
thinks that it was his fault that his family died.
他也认为是自己的错 害得家人死掉
On his birthday,
他生日
he threw a tantrum because he wanted to go to an amusement park.
撒娇说要去游乐场
They had an accident on their way home.
在回家路上遇上了意外
His parents and younger brother died
他父母和弟弟都死了
and only he survived.
只有他活下来
Of course it wasn't his fault.
这根本不是他的错
But no matter what other people tell him,
可是无论别人说什么
he still…
那家伙如今
thinks from the bottom of his heart that it was his fault.
打从心底还觉得是自己的错
But he lives
但他活下去
for himself.
是为了自己
Not for anyone else.
不是为了别人
You can still live.
他还是活下来了
Even if you're carrying a very heavy and painful burden on your shoulder,
不管背着多么沉重、悲伤的重担
you can still live for yourself.
你也可以过你的人生
As long as there is someone who would laugh with you.
只要有人在身边 就有快乐的事
I don't know…
我不晓得
whether Choco sees us as friends like that to him or not,
阿闪是不是把我们当作这样的同伴
but he is
可是那家伙
always smiling when he is with us.
跟我们在一起时 总是笑着
You've got someone who does that, too!
你明明就有这样的人 还近在身边
Futaba.
姊姊
I don't want this.
我才不要活出自己的人生
It is easy not to think about anything!
这样快乐吗？会无忧无虑吗？
It's easier to live for someone who would guide you in your life.
还不如找一个人领导 为了他而活
I know how you feel.
我懂这一点
I used to be like that, too.
我曾经也跟你一样
You… Why are you…
你怎么还活着？
Your sister saved my life.
是你妹妹救了我
She deceived the Hierarch's eyes and saved my life.
她骗过了大师 让我活了下来
I called him here, too.
是我叫他来这里的
Is that so?
这样吗？
I thought…
我觉得
maybe he could pull you out of there.
或许他能把你拉出来
You mean he could get me out of the Glorious Ark?
你想让他说服我离开光耀方舟吗？
No,
不对
I mean from the lonely cage which you went into willingly.
你钻牛角尖 把自己关进了孤独的牢笼
The cage isn't even locked. You're not confined in it.
笼子根本没上锁 没有人把你关起来
You can go out whenever you want,
你想的话 随时都可以出来
to the person who is waiting for you.
回去找一直等待你的人
After I see this matter through to its end,
这件事告一段落之后
my son and I will give ourselves up to the police.
我会跟儿子去自首
Let's go to the police together.
我们一起去警察局
Let's atone for our sins together.
一起去赎罪
Futaba…
姊姊…
You…
你这…
have betrayed us, haven't you?
是背叛
All traitors will be purified.
大师吩咐过
These are the teachings of the Hierarch.
要把叛徒当场净化
Watch out!
危险！
Futaba!
姊姊！
You…
你…
Futaba…
姊姊…
-I'll call an ambulance. -No!
-我叫救护车 -不要
It will mean trouble.
只会更麻烦
You know that, don't you?
我想你也知道这一点
Futaba, no…
姊姊 不要…
-No! -I'm sorry, Mifumi.
-不要… -对不起 美史
This is the only thing
我只能这样遵守约定…
How…
为什么事情会变成这样？
When did I start doing wrong?
我从什么时候开始错了？
Have you always been with me, Mifumi?
你一直都在…美史
Right there for me…
就在我身边
I want to start again.
我想改过自新
You can start again.
那就改过自新
No, I can't.
我不行了
I have killed too many people.
我杀了太多人
You…
你过来
Tell her…
请找一天…
someday,
对她说
tell her that…
谢谢你…
you're grateful that she is alive.
活了下来
Futaba…
姊姊…
Futaba! No!
姊姊 不要！
No!
不要！
Don't leave me, Futaba!
不要丢下我 姊姊！
-I couldn't do anything for them. -I see.
-我什么忙都帮不上 -这样啊
She said that she would take care of the rest, too.
她还说剩下的事他会处理
I wonder if Miss Mifumi will be able to leave
不知道美史小姐 能不能从光耀方舟全身而退
Don't worry.
别担心
Hikari's father will destroy them with the data anyway.
只要日花里的爸爸有存储卡 就能铲除他们
I wonder if there is anything I can do to help her.
难道我真的什么忙都帮不上吗？
Keebou.
希少
Women and children steel themselves for what they face when necessary.
你别小看女人或小孩 她们心意已决
It's rude to try to help someone who has done that.
既然她们心意已决 你这样很不尊重
You have always trusted her, haven't you?
你不是相信那小鬼才走到这一步吗？
Despite what we told you.
都不听我们的劝
Just keep trusting her.
你要相信下去 一直相信下去
TOILET
（洗手间）
I can't get it out!
不行 还是拉不出来
Let me take a break!
让我休息一会
Don't be silly! Of course you can't! Don't stop until you get it out!
白痴 拉不出来就别出来！
Don't say it like "Don't be defeated until you win!"
胜利之前决不认输
Guys, I can't do it when you're just a door away from me.
你们大呼小叫的 我反而拉不出来
Shut up, Data Boy!
闭嘴 你这人型存储卡！
If you can't get it out in ten minutes,
再过十分钟还拉不出来 就判你爆菊之刑
-Please, don't do that! -I'll execute it using my hands.
-大爷饶命 -我亲手执行
Don't do that, please spare me that!
求你放过我！
Why don't we just hand Choco himself to Mr. Goto?
干脆把阿闪交给五嶋先生吧？
How can you do that to me?
你说什么傻话？
Just wait!
喂 你们再等等
That's because you did something stupid.
谁叫你自讨苦吃
I'm sorry.
对不起
Sorry about the data.
存储卡的事实在抱歉
-But before the deadline, I'll… -It's not necessary.
-但我一定会及时… -没此必要
We will get it soon.
我过不久就能拿到存储卡
What the heck?
你这混蛋说什么？
-You have betrayed us? -Sendagi!
-你要背叛我吗？ -千驮木！
That will do it.
这样就行了
Now…
这样
Your son's life will be saved.
令郎就能活了
How we got it was a bit gross,
出处是有点恶心 但是我们已经好好消毒过了
Thank you.
谢谢
Really.
真的谢谢你们
-May I ask you something? -Yes?
-我能问你一件事吗？ -什么？
What is stored in it?
存储卡里到底有什么？
It is some news that will cause chaos in Japan
日本和全世界在一周内将看到 史上最轰动的新闻
That's what stored inside.
就在这里面
The day has finally come.
这一天终于来了
-You can look forward to it. -Okay.
-请拭目以待 -好的
Hikari,
日花里
see you again.
再见
We will. I'm sure that we'll meet again.
会再见的 一定会再见的
Please tell Choco and Ponjara to get well soon.
代我跟阿闪和碰将说 “你们要快点康复”
-Sure. -I think Choco will cry.
-好 -阿闪他一定会哭
What? Choco cries?
阿闪哥会哭吗？
I know Ponjara will bawl his eyes out, but Choco?
我想碰将哥会号啕大哭 阿闪哥不会吧
His nose would keep running when he cried, and he would cry overnight.
他鼻水会流个不停 而且会哭到早上
-His eyes would swell so much. -Seriously?
-眼睛会肿成这样 -真的假的？
Thank you, Hikari.
谢谢 日花里
Why?
-什么？ -要是没遇上你
I would never have been friends again with them.
我们就不会聚在一起
Yeah, same here.
我们也是
We would have kept feeling gloomy.
所以才解开了心里的结
Thank you, Hikari.
谢谢你 日花里
Oh, right.
对了
Please keep this.
这个送给你
-Yes? -As a token.
-咦？ -当作纪念
Oh… Thanks.
好的
Thank you so much.
真的谢谢你们
You guys really are the hope of this country.
你们真的是这国家的希望
You're exaggerating.
你过奖了
Keebou…
希少…
Forget it.
没事
Take care, Hikari.
保重 日花里
Guys, thank you.
谢谢你们大家
Thank you.
谢谢
We're reluctant to leave, but we have to go.
离别难免会依依不舍 但我们该走了
Hikari!
日花里
Take care!
保重
Keebou…
希少…
I love you.
我最喜欢你了
I love you!
最喜欢你
I love you, Keebou.
我最喜欢希少了
See you, Hikari.
再见 日花里
Welcome home.
欢迎回来
I'm home.
我回来了
-Welcome home, Pichan. -I'm home.
-小屁 欢迎回来 -我回来了
I want to buy something.
我有东西想买
Have a seat.
坐吧
I thought you said you had bought enough?
纱彩 你不是说不网购了吗？
I want to buy it! I want it! This one.
我要买东西 就这个
SATOJIMA
（里岛）
I'm home.
我回来了
Of course she is gone.
也对 她早就不在了
Toru?
阿透？
Why?
为什么？
Welcome home!
欢迎回来！
MIKI TIRES
（三木自行车）
I'm home.
我回来了
Welcome home.
欢迎回来
Enema?
爆菊吗？
-It's not funny. -It is very funny.
-一点都不好笑 -不 真的很好笑
-Mr. Tokui? -Yes?
-德井先生 -是的
Hello.
你好
You've never told me!
喂 我怎么都没听你说过？
It's not what you think, idiot!
白痴 你搞错了
It isn't?
不是吗？
I didn't mean that.
不 就是这样
How did you utter that sound?
你语气好恶心
-Shut up! -"I didn't mean that…"
-吵死了 -“就是这样”
THANK YOU FOR SAVING ME. I LOVE YOU, KEEBOU.
（谢谢你救我 我最喜欢希少了）
-Okay, I'll think about it. -Thank you!
-知道 我们会考虑的 -拜托你了
Thanks very much.
不好意思 谢谢你
Today, before dawn, a fire broke out in a hotel
千叶县成田市机场酒店 今天凌晨发生火灾
In the room where it started
起火源头是客房
bodies believed to be the two occupants were found.
现场发现两具遗体 应是投宿的父女两人
The victims of this fire seemed to be 44-year-old Yukio Goto
火灾中的死者分别是五嶋幸雄44岁
and his daughter, 10-year-old Hikari Goto.
和他十岁的长女日花里
According to the police and the fire service,
引述警察和消防员所说
the fire burnt the room, where the source of the fire was,
起火点是客房 在起火后约一小时后被扑灭
-Impossible… -but the bodies of the Gotos,
-怎么可能… -最后在房间内发现房客
who stayed in the room, where the origin of the fire was, were found.
五嶋父女的遗体
I don't believe this… You have to be kidding…
骗人的…骗人的吧？
-Did I lose? -I didn't think it would be like this.
-我输了吗？ -没想到会这样
Thank you for saving me. I love you, Keebou.
谢谢你救我 我最喜欢希少了
Please go back to you normal life.
你也回到你原本的生活吧